Oh, here. Looks like it's in exactly two weeks.
I mean, what? Two weeks? How am I supposed to build an entire outfit in two weeks?
Is she insane? It already takes me forever to make clothing for Hina dolls.
I'm sure it's gonna take at least twice as long to make something for a real live human.
Then again, I've never actually done it before, so I have no frame of reference to even estimate whether it could be possible or not.
This sucks. I have to find a way. I have to.
She's like I was looking forward to this so much. I can't disappoint her.
Anyway, I'll get on it as soon as I'm home. I'll make the patterns first and then start cutting.
Oh, jeez. How long is that gonna take?
None of the pieces can be cut in a straight line. They're all curvy.
I'll need at least two or three days. It's no use. There's not enough time.
Uh, there it goes. My mind has been lost.
Of course, Slippery Girls could have had something to do with that, too.
Yes, please.
Well, let's help.
What do you think of that is?
Good night.
See you next time.
I'm home.
Oh, good. I was worried. You're, uh, home pretty late today, aren't you?
Um, yeah, I'm sorry. I just got distracted and forgot to call.
It was fun. I went out shopping with a friend.
A friend, huh? That's excellent news, Wakana.
What were you shopping for? Some new books, maybe? Or those little record CDs?
Huh? Grandpa, are you okay?
Uh, there you are.
Thanks for coming. It's late. I'm sorry.
Hmm. How's Grandpa?
They're putting a compress on him now.
I see.
Thankfully, it wasn't too bad of a fall.
And that's it. We'll get you something for the pain.
You be careful and watch your step.
Thank you, Doctor. I appreciate all your help.
Grandpa!
Hey!
Don't scare us like that.
What on earth are you doing here, Mayori?
Just take it slow, okay?
Well, I had a blank spot in my schedule.
What? I was worried about you.
So they want you to stay in bed for two weeks?
Dad suggested that you come stay with us until you're feeling better.
I'm here to bring you home with me.
Yeah, good idea. Plus, their house is closer to the hospital anyway.
We also have a car, in case we need to take you.
All right, then. Just hope I'm not a burden.
Why don't you come spend the night with us tonight?
We've got a futon for you.
Hmm. All right. I'll bring you fresh clothes tomorrow.
Thanks. Sorry about this.
Oh, but...
My brushes. Could you bring them?
Maybe we should take you to an acupuncturist, too.
Sure.
Are you okay?
All this shaking, it's just got me shook up.
No, not okay.
I see.
So that's why you weren't at school yesterday.
Uh-huh.
So, um, I'm going by there again today to check on him.
You must be so worried.
I'd be. Hope he starts feeling better soon.
Yeah.
Hey, Gojo.
Let me know if there's anything I can do to help.
I can't sew, but I can cook and do house stuff.
Thanks, Kitagawa.
But I think I should be fine.
Still, though, it's nice of you.
Right. I get it.
Well, then, let's trade numbers at least.
We ought to have a way to reach each other if something comes up.
Uh, cool?
Yeah, sure.
I'm so far behind.
I didn't work on the outfit yesterday or the day before.
I need to do something today.
By the way, I got the wig cut and it looks super sick.
I brought it to give you.
Hey, are you there?
Huh?
Oh, of course.
Sorry.
Oh, that's right.
My gross midterms are next week.
Could this be more poorly timed?
Especially since I'm the type that needs to cram the night.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Midterms?
I completely forgot.
Somehow, between visiting Grandpa and studying for tests,
I have to find time to make an entire outfit.
Hey, Gojo.
You okay?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
I think I might be in trouble.
Hello, Gojo dolls.
How can I help you?
You mean a tour of our workshop?
Yes, that's right.
I was told that you offer tours, but if not...
Yes, ma'am.
We sure do.
Oh, that's fantastic.
My friend is very interested in Hina dolls,
so I think he would really enjoy the opportunity.
When are you guys wanting to come in?
Well, um, this is kind of a last-minute request.
We were hoping we could do it May 6th.
That's tomorrow.
Um, I'm terribly sorry.
We're actually closed until next Saturday,
but we can fit you in after that anytime you'd like.
Oh, gosh.
I wish we could,
but you see,
my friend is here visiting all the way from France.
He's actually flying home the day after tomorrow,
so unfortunately that was our only option.
Anyway, sorry to bother you.
I appreciate your help.
No, wait!
We can do it!
Come in!
Oh, really?
You can?
The shop owner's out,
but if you don't mind me doing it,
I can give you a tour after 4.30.
Are you serious?
That's great!
Thank you so much!
Of course.
Okay.
Then, uh,
I'll see you tomorrow.
What have I done?
What's wrong with me?
What do I do?
What should I do?
I...
What do I do?
All right, pencils down.
Hell yeah! We are free, my dudes!
We're done!
I should probably finish the apron and headdress first.
Hey, Marion. How'd it go?
Fine, I guess.
He's weird.
I figured he'd be home by this point.
I guess I thought wrong.
Maybe now that midterms are over, he can relax and be with his grandpa?
Oh, Gojo. I hope he's okay.
I guess it's a lonely dinner for one.
My head hurts.
I feel sick.
Like I'm gonna throw up.
I can't focus on anything.
When was the last time I really slept?
The outfit.
It's not even close to being done.
I've let her down.
Kitagawa was so excited about it.
She's gonna be heartbroken.
My brushes.
Could you bring them?
Why are you bringing your brushes on the trip?
Hmm?
Well, I have to keep these hands moving, or they'll get rusty and won't work.
If I skip even a day, it takes another three days to get the hang of it again.
I don't even know how to use them properly yet.
It's been so long since I've touched them.
Maybe I'm not cut out for it after all.
Just because you love to do something doesn't mean you do it well.
You can work hard, but that doesn't mean it'll pay off.
What am I gonna do with my life if I can't become a kashirashi?
What will Kitagawa say when she hears the outfit's not done?
Why can't I do anything right?
What a joke!
I am such a pathetic failure.
I'm just limping along, half-ashing my way through my entire life.
Hey, Grandpa.
Hmm?
Isn't it hard making Hino dolls every day?
Don't your hands hurt?
Aren't you tired of working so much?
Well, you're right.
It is hard.
Loving something doesn't make it easy to do.
But then again, it's because you love working on it that you can stick it out when things get rough.
Whenever I see our customers smile, I'm grateful I chose to do this, beautiful.
Look.
Whoa.
When what you do makes someone happy, that makes you want to keep going, even if it's hard.
Hey, Gojo.
You're the best.
It's fine not to compromise.
I've got some things I'm pretty hardcore about, too.
Hell yeah!
Where's the first place I should wear it once it's complete?
You saved me so much time.
And money, too.
Thank you.
I need scissors.
Where are they?
Don't tell me they're missing.
I need scissors.
No way.
It was a close call, but it's finished somehow, and you can go to your event.
Hold on.
What are you saying?
You thought I wanted to cosplay at today's event?
What?
So you mean you're not?
I mean, I...
I had absolutely no idea how long it takes to make clothing.
And there are actually quite a few cosplay events around if you search for them.
Since I didn't know what our timeline was, I was just gonna wait until you were finished.
I am so sorry.
I didn't realize I wasn't clear.
Now you're exhausted because of me.
Oh, wow.
That's such a relief.
I was so anxious about not finishing, so I rushed through it.
I'm thrilled there's still some time.
Oh, thank goodness.
For real.
Oh.
Huh?
Wait, what'd I do?
No, it's just that during exams, you said you went home to study, but I thought you were visiting your grandpa.
I didn't know.
I'm such an idiot.
I should have realized.
You've been dealing with so much, and somehow you still made time to finish the outfit.
I'm sorry.
I promise.
I had no idea you were doing that for me.
Please, forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, so, uh, I'm sorry, too.
I should have let you know what I was doing.
That's why we exchanged numbers, right?
This is all my fault for not being clear.
No, it's not.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Really.
Come on.
Hey, please, don't cry.
So, um, why don't you try it on?
Let's make sure it fits.
Now that there's more time, I can tailor it properly and see if anything needs taking in.
Oh, yeah.
We should also see how everything looks all together.
Put your wig on and makeup, too.
What?
You want me to do it right now?
But you're totally exhausted, aren't you?
Listen to me.
Huh?
We gotta focus.
You want to become Shizuku-tan, don't you?
Yeah, you know I do.
Then you need to try it on.
I can't be satisfied with my work unless I know you're happy with the final product.
It's really the only thing that matters to me.
So, tell me the truth.
Are you happy with it?
Of course, I love it so much.
It's perfect.
Really, I'm more than happy.
Thank you so much, Kojo.
Sure.
I'm serious.
It means so much to me.
I swear I'm gonna wear the hell out of it.
I'll make you proud.
Great.
Get it all out.
Got it.
I feel much better now, thanks.
There you go.
So, how you doing?
Got your makeup off?
Yep.
In that case, we'll draw your brows kinda droopy, and then do a red eyeshadow look.
Your blush should come right underneath your eyes, and then we'll do a neutral lip to make them stand out.
But just that part will be soft.
Everything else will be more dramatic to help tie it in with the outfit.
So, it's like that sick girl makeup?
Sick girl?
First, stretch out the eye tape.
Then gently place it where you want the crease of your eyelid.
Who would ever think to change the shape of their eyelids?
I would.
I even have the same eye tape.
Huh?
What for?
I wanted to try it for a while there, but I never got around to it.
I see.
You know, falsies would be great.
The winged ones that are longer on the ends would also give you that droopy look.
Then you would definitely look like Shizukatari.
That sucks.
I don't have false lashes.
I tried them once, but they were hard to put on.
That's okay.
I have some you can use.
What?
We have a few different styles.
Oh, perfect.
Winged ones, too.
Uh...
Is something wrong?
So, are these your girlfriends?
No!
Uh, of course not!
Some Hina dolls are made with lashes these days.
It's like a whole thing.
I got these to try it.
It makes a difference, see?
Aw, she's adorable!
I would have been psyched if someone got me a doll that looked like this when I was little.
And her kimonos got roses on it!
There are some that are painted with pink or orange lipstick now.
Some are wearing blush.
Some of them even have light brown highlights in their black hair.
And I've even seen blonde ones.
It's amazing the way they're evolving.
Wow!
That one is so cute!
I love her style.
Hina dolls can be hard to tell apart.
But Grandpa, he can tell you who the maker is just by the way the eyebrows are drawn.
Impressive!
But, if you see a Hina doll that looks like this, you immediately know who made her.
I hope...
I hope one day, I can do it too, you know?
Make dolls that look this beautiful.
Uh, not that this is of any importance right now.
It'll happen.
Trust me.
You'll get there, Gojo.
I know you will.
Wow, thanks for saying that.
Oh, so that's what it looks like when you smile, huh?
This is the first time I've seen you do it for real.
What?
That's not true.
My smiles are always real, see?
I'm smiling now.
So, um, what do you want to do for eyebrows?
Shizukutans aren't shaped like yours, so...
We might have to get rid of them.
Well, good thing Aiguro's back, am I right?
She shaved them off!
Hey, uh, Gojo?
Hmm?
You ready to see it?
What do you think?
Did it work?
Do I...
Do I look like Shizukutan?
Huh?
Yes!
You really do.
You're the perfect Shizukutan.
You're right!
I am!
I can feel it!
Thank you, Gojo!
I'm totally Shizukutan right now!
You are!
You're totally Shizukutan right now!
Don't let me finish!
covid-dous Alex!
I'm sorry...
Look!
I understand!
I'm soakterist ii!
What's this?
Jetzt me try...
I love you!
We'll now...
Thank you.